Philipp Pisarevskiy

Skilled Product Designer

About me

I am a BA Product Design graduate from UAL, world's 6th art and design university, according to QS World University Rakings.

After almost 4 years of practice working with clients on various design tasks and gaining international academic experience over several years, I am looking for the next opportunity to expand and apply my range of skills and knowledge.

Skills and interests

Product, industrial and communication design development and production, presenting, prototyping and modelling.

Market & user research, analysis, trend forecasting, consulting, advertising and marketing.

CAD and class A modeling, CAM, engineering, design for manufacture, technical drawing to GOST and BSI.

Information technology, mathematics, applied science, machine learning, programming (Obj-C, C++/#, Swift, Python, PHP, JS, HTML, Matlab, Bash)

Software

CG 3ds max, Vray, Keyshot, 3D Coat, Substance Designer, HDR Studio, Maya, Houdini, Zbrush.

CAD Solidworks, Rhino, Grasshopper, Alias, CATIA, Siemens NX, Inventor.

2D Adobe Ps, Ai, Id, Ae, Pr, Dw, Corel.

Contacts

tel: +44 7935 146 787 +7 912 340 79 98

email: philipp@yoursdesigner.com portfolio: yoursdesigner.com

Education

Central Saint Martins College of Art and Design

BA (Hons) Product Design, 1st Class Honours 2016 - 2018, London, UK

British Higher School Of Art And Design

BA (Hons) Product Design 2015 - 2016, Moscow, Russia

Central Saint Martins College of Art and Design

Foundation in Art and Design 2014 - 2015, London, UK

John Leggott College

A-levels in Further Maths, Design & Technology and Computing 2013 - 2014, Scunthorpe, UK

Experience

Co-Founder, Seamless

2016 - present, Moscow, Russia

Building a retail experience startup, along with a team of an experienced IT entrepreneur and an economist. So far have done market and trend research, business planning, brand communication, attracting investors. Currently, doing R&D work in data collection algorithms, backend and front end system prototypinga and negotiating with retailers over testing the system.

Competition finalist, design project for Zumtobel

2017, London, UK

Created a range of luminaires, starting from user-centered research, through to resolving technical documentation and engineering. The design was proposing a way to make artificial light more tangible.

2nd prize winner, design project for MTS Russia

2016, Moscow, Russia

Worked along with a group of students to design a kiosk for a large telecom company. We have proposed a concept for 2020, which had taken the 2nd prize in the competition and has later turned into startup company Seamless, which specialises in retail experience.

Designer and consultant (contract), Orenburg Regional Television 2015, Orenburg, Russia

Consulted a local TV channel over rebranding and lead the development towards production of souvenirs and production for broadcast.

Lead designer and consultant (contract), Ministry of Economics

2014 - 2016, Orenburg, Russia

Together with local government, developed a brand idenity for use in external and internal events. I was invited to work after a public competition, in which my work has taken the first prize, and after that, continued working on developing the brand and passing the guidelines to the design team on the client side.

